

# **ABOUT**

This is Rishabh Tripathi and I'm a Professional Musician, Teacher, Producer, Vocalist, Multi-Instrumentalist for over 12 Years with decent performance experience and knowledge of In-depth Musical Theory. As an all-time Musician I believe the music has to be taught in a proper & easy way to understand the deep roots of Musical Culture and Theory and that's how I developed the interest in Teaching Music also and now it has been more than 7 Years since. I teach Guitars, Piano and Vocals

#### CONTACT

+919675177634 rishabh0796@gmail.com

# **SKILLS**

- Guitars
- Piano/Keyboard
- Western Vocals
- Music Theory
- Music Production

# RISHABH TRIPATHI

# MUSIC INSTRUCTOR

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **BodhiTree School of Music**

Music Teacher, Author (Trinity Curriculum) 2024-Present

#### **NeoWave Records**

Music Teacher, Music Producer 2022-2024

#### R7's

Music Teacher 2016-2018

# Infeeds

Music Blogger 2015-2020

## **EDUCATION**

# Asian Academy of Film & Television

Music Production 2018-2019

#### Noida School of Rock

Western Vocals, Music Theory 2015-2016

#### **Doon Cambridge School**

Intermediate 1999-2014

### **CERTIFICATIONS**

**RSL Grades**: Western Vocals, Music Production

**Diploma:** Music Production